anime4fun.com 2016-09-19

# Watch Anime online with english sub - animeonline

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Animeonline.us is committed to protecting your privacy to allow for a safe and secure experience for our viewer. If we were to ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using our website. You can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The general use of this information is for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement click-through, and other activities on the website by using cookies, web beacons, and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. The actions of such parties and how they use such information is subject to the particular third party’s privacy policy. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
